They're too human to be perfect. She's too perfect to be human.
Wifelike is a science fiction, mystery, thriller film directed by James Bird.
A grieving detective in the near-future hunts down criminals
who trade artificial humans on the black market.
In the fight to end AI exploitation, an underground resistance attempts to infiltrate him by sabotaging the
programming of the artificial human assigned as his companion to behave like his late wife.
She begins to question her reality as memories of a past life begin
to surface in a world where nothing is as it seems.
Meredith, played by Elena Kampouris.
William, played by Jonathan Rhys Meyers.
Agent Black, played by Doron Bell.
Louise, played by Agam Darshi.
Wendy, played by Sara Sampaio.
Lydie, played by Alix Villaret.
Wifelike is a 2022 American science fiction thriller film written and directed by
James Bird and starring Jonathan Rhys Meyers and Elena Kampouris.
The film explores themes of artificial intelligence
(a.i.), robot girl, near future, robot wife.
The tone is intense and thought_provoking and mind_bending.